## CORRI GOLDEN

Software Developer

615-756-1127 corri.golden@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/corri-golden/ github.com/corri-golden corri-golden.github.io

#### PROFILE

Throughout my career, I've had the opportunity to work with either my creative or analytical side. Software Development has been the only career that has allowed me to utilize both. When introduced to coding in 2018, I spent a lot of time learning with online resources. Upon hearing about software bootcamps, I was convinced it was time to dive head first into a career that fully utilizes all my strengths.

#### **TECH USED**

- Javascript
- Visual Studio Code
- React
- SQL
- Python and Django JSON
  - BootStrap
- HTML
- . . . . .
- CSS
- ReactStrap
- GitHub -Agile
- Material UI

#### INDIVIDUAL PROJECT: KEEPUP

KeepUp is a single page application that allows transportation business owners to KeepUp with the maintenance issues of the cars employees are assigned to. It's a React built CRUD functionality app where users are able to add, edit, and delete maintenance issues.

Also used: Material UI and ReactStrap

#### LANGUAGES

English, Spanish, French

#### **EDUCATION**

NASHVILLE SOFTWARE SCHOOL | 2020 Software Development Bootcamp, Certificate

#### TENNESSEE STATE UNIVERSITY | DEC 2009

Bachelor's: Business Administration & Real Estate Development

#### EXPRIENCE

#### SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

NASHVILLE SOFTWARE SCHOOL | OCT '19 - PRESENT

Intensive full-time 6-month software development bootcamp designed to teach Python/Django, JavaScript, React, SQL, problem solving, and working in teams.

#### Group Project:

Nutshell - React

- Created a social media dashboard application that allows users to send messages, events, articles, and tasks
- Single page, CRUD application created with React, Bootstrap, Javascript, and JSON-Servers through API fetch calls
- Personally responsible for the messages section, which implemented CRUD functionality so users are able to create, edit, and delete messages with timestamps onto the DOM

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### PROPERTY/ASSISTANT PROPERTY MANAGER

JLL | MAR 2017 - JUL 2019

- Assisted Property Manager collect revenue, decreasing delinquency \$300,000 in one year.
- Managed 1.1 million square foot industrial property and assisted Property Manager in managing 800,000 square foot medical/retail/office center
- Assisted to minimize budget expenses leading to increased NOI by 15% over three quarters
- Prepared annual operating budgets and prepared quarterly variance reports for different accounts

#### **OPERATIONS MANAGER**

GC LOGISTICS, LLC | MAR 2015 - FEB 2017

- Brokered new contract with a Non-emergency Transportation company that lead to 10% increase in profits
- Maximized driver time and efficiency by implementing route optimization apps to lower operating expenses and increase NOI
- Responsible for computer data entry such as invoice processing, corrections, ad doc tracking/control, and vehicle management
- On-boarded and trained new drivers the companies' policy, which includes safety procedures and wheelchair securement training

\_\_

# CORRIGOLDEN

### Software Developer

#### **EXPERIENCE CONTINUED**

#### DATABASE SPECIALIST

ANYTHING POWERSPORTS | DEC 2012 - FEB 2015

- Tracked and analyzed products sales across each e-commerce sites to identify the rate of conversion
- Responsible for converting products' data from manufacturers to sale at e-commerce and company websites
- Managed products in the database to sell on both eBay and Amazon
- Created product content and styling for the Anything PowerSports website

#### PROMOTIONAL/EXPERIENTIAL MARKETING

PRODUCTION/TOUR MANAGER | MAR 2010 - DEC 2012

- Assisted with planning, and coordination of nationwide events to improve brand recognition and generate sales for companies like Geico, Cisco, and Texas on Tour
- Managed a staff of ten to ensure the user experience and branding message was consistent with the clients specifications
- Responsible for logistics of marketing materials, facilities, and staff for tours across the United States
- Oversaw the production process at each event